{"status":"Success","data":{"general_datas":[{"q_number":"76","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7e"},{"q_number":"77","question":"\u0d06\u0d27\u0d41\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d7b\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"78","question":"\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d2b \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"1904- \u0d38\u0d42\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"79","question":"\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d2b\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d07\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f \u0d07\u0d7b\u0d2b\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4b"},{"q_number":"80","question":"\u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d02 ?","answer":"2.44 m \u0d05\u0d15\u0d32\u0d02 - 7.32 m"},{"q_number":"81","question":"\u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 ?","answer":"410 to 450 g"},{"q_number":"82","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d7e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"83","question":"\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d31\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d4d- 1930"},{"q_number":"84","question":"\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d31\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d31\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d28"},{"q_number":"85","question":"\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d47\u0d26\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d31\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"86","question":"\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e ?","answer":"13"},{"q_number":"87","question":"\u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"4"},{"q_number":"88","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d1f\u0d40\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d02 ?","answer":"23"},{"q_number":"89","question":"\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d 32 \u0d1f\u0d40\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"1998 \u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"90","question":"\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"21"},{"q_number":"91","question":"88 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d ?","answer":"8"},{"q_number":"92","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d24\u0d35\u0d23 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d40\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d40\u0d7d (5 \u0d24\u0d35\u0d23 )"},{"q_number":"93","question":" \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d40\u0d7d 21(\u0d1c\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f - 19)"},{"q_number":"94","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d1f\u0d40\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f (106) 2\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d7d - 104"},{"q_number":"95","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d1f\u0d40\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f - 224 ( \u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d40\u0d7d- 211)"},{"q_number":"96","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02 ?","answer":"5"},{"q_number":"97","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d28\u0d47\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f (1938)"},{"q_number":"98","question":"\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15"},{"q_number":"99","question":"\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d7d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c -18 (Adidas)"},{"q_number":"100","question":"\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d2b \u0d31\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"1992 "},{"q_number":"101","question":"\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d2b \u0d31\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"102","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d31\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d7c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1f\u0d40\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d40\u0d7d"},{"q_number":"103","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1f\u0d40\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d25\u0d47\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d47 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d1f\u0d40\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d40\u0d7d"},{"q_number":"104","question":"\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d14\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"1962 - \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"105","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d31\u0d2b\u0d31\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d36\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c "},{"q_number":"106","question":"\u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"2002(\u0d1c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7b, \u0d38\u0d57\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f)"},{"q_number":"107","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d0f\u0d15 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d37 \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"108","question":"\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"1991- \u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28"},{"q_number":"109","question":"\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d37-\u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d1f\u0d40\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"110","question":"\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d32\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 ?","answer":"my life and beautiful game"},{"q_number":"111","question":"\u0d2e\u0d31\u0d21\u0d4b\u0d23 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 ?","answer":"I am the \r\nDiego\r\n"},{"q_number":"112","question":"\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e ?","answer":"escape to victory"},{"q_number":"113","question":"\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d1f\u0d40\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"1948"},{"q_number":"114","question":"\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d7a \u0d21\u0d3f \u0d13\u0d7c \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d24\u0d35\u0d23 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f (5)"},{"q_number":"115","question":"2014 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f (\u0d31\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d31\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d - \u0d05\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d28 )"},{"q_number":"116","question":"2022 \u0d32\u0d46 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d16\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d7c"},{"q_number":"514","question":"\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d3f.\u0d38\u0d3f. 776\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"515","question":"\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d15\u200c\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d48\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d18\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?\r\n","answer":"10\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"516","question":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d48\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d18\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?\r\n","answer":"3000 \u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"517","question":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d42\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?\r\n","answer":"42.195 \u0d15\u0d3f.\u0d2e\u0d40.( 26\u0d2e\u0d48\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d385\u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f)\r\n"},{"q_number":"518","question":"\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d13\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d38\u0d4d (\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d)\r\n"},{"q_number":"519","question":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d38\u0d4d - \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\r\n"},{"q_number":"520","question":"\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d26\u0d48\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d18\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d24\u0d4d\u200c\u0d32\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 50\u0d15\u0d3f.\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02\r\n"},{"q_number":"521","question":"\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d31\u0d47\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"522","question":"\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"523","question":"\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d46\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d42\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d15 (\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d48\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d) \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d24\u0d35\u0d23 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d31\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"35 \u0d24\u0d35\u0d23\r\n"},{"q_number":"608","question":"\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d2b(FIFA)\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n","answer":"202\r\n"},{"q_number":"609","question":"\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d2b \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"1930 \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d31\u0d42\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d47\r\n"},{"q_number":"610","question":"\u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d47\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d28 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d57\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\r\n"},{"q_number":"611","question":"1982 \u0d21\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d39\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d30\u0d46 , \u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d47\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d02\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d28 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d17\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d46\u0d21\u0d31\u0d47\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"637","question":"\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d3f.\u0d38\u0d3f.776\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"638","question":"\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d15\u200c\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46\u0d26\u0d48\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d18\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?\r\n","answer":"10\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"639","question":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d48\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d18\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02\u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?\r\n","answer":"3000 \u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"640","question":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d42\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?\r\n","answer":"42.195 \u0d15\u0d3f.\u0d2e\u0d40.(26\u0d2e\u0d48\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d385\u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f)\r\n"},{"q_number":"641","question":"\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d13\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d38\u0d4d(\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d)\r\n"},{"q_number":"642","question":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d38\u0d4d- \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\r\n"},{"q_number":"643","question":"\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d26\u0d48\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d18\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d05\u0d24\u0d4d\u200c\u0d32\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4650\u0d15\u0d3f.\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02\r\n"},{"q_number":"644","question":"\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46\u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d31\u0d47\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"645","question":"\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"646","question":"\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d38\u0d46\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d42\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d15 (\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d48\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d)\u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d24\u0d35\u0d23 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d31\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"35 \u0d24\u0d35\u0d23\r\n"},{"q_number":"653","question":"\u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d17\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d21\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d41 (1970)\r\n"},{"q_number":"654","question":"\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d21\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3f\r\n"},{"q_number":"657","question":"\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d21\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d46\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"803","question":"\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d\r\n \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41.?","answer":"\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"804","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d08 \u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e ISL \u0d7d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02.\u0d1f\u0d40\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d48\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d1a\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d31"},{"q_number":"805","question":"\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d40\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d46\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"1928"},{"q_number":"806","question":"I0C ( \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d23\u0d7d \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f ) \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d27\u0d3f ?","answer":"8 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02"},{"q_number":"807","question":"\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2f\u0d42\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"2010 Singapore"},{"q_number":"808","question":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d7a \u0d35\u0d46\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d7d \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d21\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2b\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d41\u0d30\u0d47\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d41\r\n"},{"q_number":"809","question":"\u0d0e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d17\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f ?","answer":"Kim Hwayang Chill(2006)"},{"q_number":"810","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2b\u0d41\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d7e"},{"q_number":"811","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d40\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d40\u0d32\u0d15\u0d7b ?","answer":"John right\r\n"},{"q_number":"812","question":"Sudden death \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d7e\r\n"},{"q_number":"813","question":"\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"814","question":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d46\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 ?","answer":"Nadiya komanechi\r\n"},{"q_number":"815","question":"\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d7d \u0d2b\u0d48\u0d28\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d37"},{"q_number":"816","question":"\u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d ?","answer":"1900- \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"817","question":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\r\n"},{"q_number":"818","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d39\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"819","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d7d\u0d2c\u0d7a"},{"q_number":"820","question":"\u0d16\u0d47\u0d7d \u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 .\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 ?","answer":"KM \u0d2c\u0d40\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d7e"},{"q_number":"821","question":"\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"822","question":" 2017 \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d2b \u0d05\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7c 17 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d35\u0d47\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d46\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"823","question":"2016\u0d7d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d2c\u0d21\u0d3f \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d7c\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"824","question":"\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d37\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d36\u0d47\u0d37\u0d02 \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2b\u0d48\u0d28\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 ?","answer":"Lalita Babar"},{"q_number":"825","question":" IAAF \u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d7e\u0d21\u0d4d \r\n\u0d05\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d3f \u0d07\u0d2f\u0d7c \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d 2016\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d09\u0d38\u0d48\u0d7b \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"826","question":"\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7d 10000 \u0d31\u0d7a\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d32\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c.\u0d15\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"827","question":" l AAF \u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d7e\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d3f \u0d07\u0d2f\u0d7c \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d40\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d17\u0d31\u0d3f 2016\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f"},{"q_number":"828","question":"\u0d09\u0d38\u0d48\u0d7b \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d47\u0d7e\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"6"},{"q_number":"829","question":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"1924"},{"q_number":"830","question":"\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f Theodotius \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d3fo\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e ?","answer":"AD 393"},{"q_number":"831","question":"2011 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d47\u0d7e\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e. \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b: \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"832","question":"2010 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d7a \u0d35\u0d46\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d7d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d7d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d21\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02 ?","answer":"38"},{"q_number":"833","question":"\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d7d\u0d2d\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"834","question":"\u0d31\u0d38\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d23\u0d7d \u0d17\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d24\u0d41\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\r\n"},{"q_number":"835","question":"\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d1f\u0d3f ?","answer":"Willow wood"},{"q_number":"836","question":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 '\u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d32\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7e"},{"q_number":"837","question":"\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d7b\u0d15\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"GV \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d7b\r\n"},{"q_number":"838","question":"KCA \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d07\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46. \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d ?","answer":"TC Mathew\r\n"},{"q_number":"839","question":"\u0d35\u0d47\u0d7e\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d39\u0d48\u0d2f\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d35\u0d31\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b ?","answer":"V. V Richards"},{"q_number":"840","question":"1900 \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d35\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"841","question":"KCA \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d39\u0d46\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02"},{"q_number":"842","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d40\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d24\u0d32\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d36\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"843","question":"ISL \u0d2b\u0d48\u0d28\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d7d\u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"844","question":"ISL \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d7a \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d25\u0d3e \u0d05\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"845","question":"\u0d35\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d23\u0d7d \u0d17\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d32\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15"},{"q_number":"846","question":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 Snooker \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02 ?","answer":"6"},{"q_number":"847","question":"\u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d7c\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f 6 \u0d1f\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7d. \u0d38\u0d46\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d31\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"848","question":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02 ?","answer":"8"},{"q_number":"849","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f 20-20 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d7e\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d32\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d35\u0d7c \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"Jogeendar sharma"},{"q_number":"850","question":"\u0d32\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d2b \u0d31\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?","answer":"97"},{"q_number":"851","question":"2016 \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d21\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?","answer":"67"},{"q_number":"852","question":"\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d48"},{"q_number":"853","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d05\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"854","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d24\u0d35\u0d23 \u0d0e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d17\u0d46\u0d02 \u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d25\u0d47\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"855","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c ?","answer":"I.M.Vijayan"},{"q_number":"856","question":"\u0d15\u0d2c\u0d21\u0d3f .\u0d1f\u0d40\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d09\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"9"},{"q_number":"857","question":"Polo \u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c ?","answer":"4"},{"q_number":"858","question":"\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7c \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c ?","answer":"7"},{"q_number":"859","question":"\u0d35\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f' \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c ?","answer":"6"},{"q_number":"860","question":"\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 cricket \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f \/ \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f"},{"q_number":"861","question":"2015 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2f\u0d41 \u0d0e \u0d07 \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7b\r\n"},{"q_number":"862","question":"\u0d38\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d1f\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d21\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d21\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d0e \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c"},{"q_number":"863","question":"20-20 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"2003"},{"q_number":"864","question":"\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f IPL \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d40\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1f\u0d40\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d7d\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"865","question":"Test \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d7b\r\n"},{"q_number":"866","question":"\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d39\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b ?","answer":"\u0d39\u0d7c\u0d2d\u0d1c\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"867","question":"ICC \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d26\u0d41\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"868","question":"\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d07\u0d28o ?","answer":"\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d1f\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"869","question":"\u0d31\u0d4b \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d24\u0d41\u0d34\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d35\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d41\u0d34\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"870","question":"\u0d38\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4b \u0d17\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"871","question":"\u0d05\u0d2f\u0d7a \u0d2c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7c\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d48 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d38\u0d48\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d46\u0d39\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7d"},{"q_number":"872","question":"2013 \u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d2b\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d47\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d02"},{"q_number":"873","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f. \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d02 ? ","answer":"\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d7d\u0d2b\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"874","question":"7 \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d02 5 \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d16\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d32\u0d3e \u0d1a\u0d57\u0d27\u0d30\u0d3f (\u0d1c\u0d32 \u0d31\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d3f )"},{"q_number":"875","question":"\u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d40\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 ?","answer":"\u0d06\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39"},{"q_number":"876","question":"\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d57\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02 ?","answer":"300 \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"877","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d39\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d28 ?","answer":"\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f"},{"q_number":"878","question":"\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d02 ? ","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 5 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d35\u0d33\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e"},{"q_number":"879","question":"\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ? ","answer":"\u0d39\u0d40\u0d30 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"880","question":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d3f .\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c"}]},"code":"100"}